<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Meta on tealblu's archive</title><link>https://tealblu.github.io/categories/meta/</link><description>Recent content in Meta on tealblu's archive</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tealblu.github.io/categories/meta/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Deployment</title><link>https://tealblu.github.io/pages/deployment/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tealblu.github.io/pages/deployment/</guid><description>How to deploy to this site: From Logseq, use schrodinger to export all public pages.
Unzip the new archive and move the new &amp;lsquo;pages&amp;rsquo; folder into tealblu.github.io/content.
May also need to copy the &amp;lsquo;assets&amp;rsquo; folder from the /logseq/ directory to the /content/ directory. Inside tealblu.github.io, open a terminal and run hugo
Create a new commit and push to the remote graph.
Wait a few minutes for Github Actions to run.</description></item><item><title>Graph Structure</title><link>https://tealblu.github.io/pages/graph-structure/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tealblu.github.io/pages/graph-structure/</guid><description>Current graph state: Structure Specification: Architecture The graph should consist of multiple hub-and-spoke structures.
The &amp;ldquo;hubs&amp;rdquo; in this system will be called root pages.
The &amp;ldquo;spokes&amp;rdquo; in this system will be called child pages.
Guidelines Any block larger than one paragraph (subjective) should be its own page.
Any page longer than two full screens should be split up.
Full sentences should be used when possible.
No orphan pages should ever be pushed to production.</description></item><item><title>Templates</title><link>https://tealblu.github.io/pages/templates/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tealblu.github.io/pages/templates/</guid><description>Templates can be used to provide structure to an otherwise unstructured graph. They are relatively self-explanatory - by using a slash command (/template), I can choose which template I want and then paste it anywhere in the file that I have open.
For more information, check the official Logseq documentation. metadata template:: metadata template-including-parent:: false
date:: YYYY-MM-DD category:: keywords:: public:: true diary template:: diary template-including-parent:: false
#Diaries &amp;lt;% today %&amp;gt; &amp;lt;% time %&amp;gt;:</description></item></channel></rss>